misshaus.com 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy

##### 1\. Personal Information

MisshaUS.com collects Personal Information which customers voluntarily submit when registering, such as, but not limited to, a person's name and email address that is necessary for MisshaUS.com to provide services offered on our site, including prompt delivery. Additionally Personal Information will include mailing address, demographic information, and preferences. All information will be used by MisshaUS.com internally to study consumers' patterns and trends and to create better site content, promotions, or other miscellaneous conditions that could aid in serving our customers more efficiently. Election of being added on to our email list will be at the customers' discretion. Once a customer elects to be included in our email list and promotional or other events sponsored by MisshaUS.com, we will collect personal information through our registration process and may also collect additional information via outside sources. All such collected information will be used to communicate and share with our customers about current promotion procedures or winning selections, our service updates, special opportunities, and future promotional events. If the customer does not wish to receive these communications, one can simply click on the "UNSUBSCRIBE" button in our email.  
When you visit MisshaUS.com, MisshaUS.com automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse MisshaUS.com, MisshaUS.com collects information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to MisshaUS.com, and information about how you interact with MisshaUS.com. We refer to this automatically-collected information as "Device Information". 

We collect the Device Information using the following technologies: "Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. "Log files" track actions occurring on MisshaUS.com, and collects data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. "Web beacons", "tags", and "pixels" are electronic files used to record information about how you browse MisshaUS.com. 

##### 2\. How We Protect Personal Information

Personal information is secured from unauthorized access from the Internet through the market leading Firewall Technology. Customer information is safeguarded within the network with the best security technology and only selected staff members with authorization will be allowed to view personal information. Any personal information provided by customers are also protected by the best security technology available and transmitted to MisshaUS.com database through a secure code.

##### 3\. How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We use the Order Information that we collect to fulfill any orders placed through MisshaUS.com (including processing your payment information, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;  
Create an account for you on MisshaUS.com;  
Identify you as a user on MisshaUS.com;  
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud;  
Improve our products or services; and  
Provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize MisshaUS.com (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with MisshaUS.com, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). 

##### 4\. Use of Cookies

Cookies are small computer files that our computer sends to a customer's computer hardware and that your computer sends back to us each time you make a request from our site. It is not necessary to use cookies to view MisshaUS.com's website. This site does use cookies. However, we do not keep any of your personal details on cookies. We simply store your Customer ID (just a number) in cookie format. This Customer ID does not correlate to any of your personal information. We also store your first name on cookie format to personalize this website. This cookie is only present if you have not registered as a member of our site. If you are a member, then the only cookie that we use is the Customer ID cookie. 

##### 5\. User's Private Information Disclosure

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use MisshaUS.com--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. 

You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful requests for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

##### 6\. Underage Users (Minors)

We acknowledge that minors (individuals under 18 years of age) are using the Internet. Thus, we encourage these children to have parental or guardian permissions prior to disclosing Personal Information or to participating in our events or promotions. However, we do believe parents or guardians should play a central role in their child's online activities and should monitor those activities to ensure that sites visited by their child are respecting their child's privacy. We suggest using those On-Line Services or software that controls children's online activities by preventing children from giving out names, addresses, and other personal information without parental permissions. 

All minor users are required to provide us with the same Personal Information as ones required for Adults in order to register with us and to participate in our events or promotions. However, we reserve the right to decline registration or to ask for parental permissions depending on the age of the users.  
Using cookies as mentioned previously, MisshaUS.com might collect data regarding children's Private Information. Such collected data is used to provide the service appropriate and popular for children.   
In pursuant to the law, MisshaUS.com is required to protect Personal Information of all minors. All Private Information is kept in secured network and only authorized staffs have access to this information.   
All parents or guardians wishing to view their children's Private Information in our database shall submit legal proof of their parental or guardian status to us. 

##### 7\. Changing and Removing Personal Information and Other Information

We are committed to giving you control over your Personal Information. You can change or remove any of the Personal Information in our database. You can correct, update, or remove information and preferences you have shared with us by utilizing Personal Information Menu.

##### 8\. User's Consent

Once a user visits our site, you automatically give us your consent for collection and use of your Private Information. We may change this policy from time to time. If we decide to change this policy in a material way, we will post notice of the change on our site via pop-up screen. You may be able to see these changes fully and comprehensively.

##### 9\. Special Events, Questionnaires and Surveysn

On occasion, MisshaUS.com may sponsor special events (such as contests, sweepstakes or other offerings), questionnaires and surveys. There may be specific rules applicable to these promotions that explain how any personal information you provide will be processed. We strongly suggest you review any applicable rules before participating. To the extent any special event, questionnaire or survey is not subject to specific rules, the processing of personal information is governed by this Privacy Policy for the purposes set forth herein.
